Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Records 6185
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Air Cleaners (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, pamphlets with info on air cleaners.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Air Quality/Correspondence, 1992-2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Correspondence Newspaper clippings, articles and correspondence requesting and relaying information on IAQ.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Air Quality Information (pt.1), 1987-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Pamphlets, memos and training material dealing with IAQ.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Air Quality information (pt.2) (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Asbestos, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Newspaper and magazine articles about asbestos in the workplace.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Back injuries, 1990-1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Newspaper and magazine articles.Pamplets and informational memos relating information on back injuries and ergonomics.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Bioaerosois (Mold, Fungus), 1994-2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, articles, pamphlets, newspaper and magazine clippings - discussing kinds of molds & fungus -- ways to detect it and ways to get rid of it.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Bioaerosois (Other), 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Articles about various bioaerosois.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Carbonless Copy Paper, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Correspondence and articles with information about Carbonless Copy Paper and hazards it causes. "NIOSH Hazard Review: Carbonless Copy Paper" by US Dept. of Health and Human Services.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Carpeting, 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Newspaper clippings, articles and correspondence giving information on the dangers of new carpeting and health problems.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - Copiers & Printers, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Articles and correspondence discussing health risks related to copiers and printers.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Office Work - IAQ (Indoor Air Quality), 1993-1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Articles and correspondence discussing possible health issues connected to IAQ.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - OSHA forms (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Copies of blank "Notice of Alleged Safety or Health Hazards" forms.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Page - Comparative (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Job descriptions, survey, wage scales from different areas used to compare the position of a Page in the library.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Planned Parenthood, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Correspondence and paperwork about possible health & safety concerns and training to help.Copy of results of a walk-thru.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Presentations, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Notes used to put together health & safety training sessions
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Reconstruction Home (IAM 1608), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Notes and correspondence about a back clinic planned by TCLC for the staff at the Reconstruction Home.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Red Cross, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  Paperwork submitted to OSHA about health and safety concersn. Correspondence about possible concerns at the Red Cross. Copy of the agreement between Tompkins County Chapter and UAW Local 2300, newspaper clippings.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Red Cross - Exposure control, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Correspondence on concerns and information on training for exposure to diseases. Memos and articles with information on the kinds of exposures and ways to reduce occurances.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Right-to-know, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Correspondence and notes about individuals rights when it comes to workplace hazards and accidents.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Karen Schlanger, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Copies of resume & correspondence about her working with TCLC.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Social Security Disabilities Benefits (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Several pamphlets explaining disability benefits in NYS.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - South Seneca Schools, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Notes and correspondence on some health problems being caused by construction at South Seneca Jr/Sr High School.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases -- Suit Kote, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Notes, memos, correspondence, news articles about Charles Streeter's death on Rt. 81 when a front end loader flipped.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - TCLC training in Tompkins County, 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Memos and correspondence outlining training offered at different businesses in Tompkins County. Copy of the Tompkins County Board of REpresentatives Vision Statement.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Teamster Local #65 (Chauffeurs, Teamsters, Warehousemen & Helpers), 1983- 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Correspondence and articles discussing health and safety concerns for the dairy industry and UPS workers.Injury reports from Crowley Farms, Polly-O and Steuben Foods. Correspondence and violation notifications.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Therm/Spill - Varsol, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Newspaper articles, correspondence about what Therm produces and for whom.Correspondence and articles about a chemical spill of Varsol.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - Tompkins County Mental Health Building, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Health & Safety -- Local cases - Tompkins County Mental Health BuildingInformation sheets, correspondence, and finished assessment report on the indoor air quality at the Mental Health Bldg.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases -- Trumansburg Head Start, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Newspaper clippings and memos/correspondence about the abrupt closing of the Head Start in Trumansburg and possible health hazards due to air quality.Memo and notes detailing actual inspection and findings. Correspondence to parents.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases - UAW Articles, Information, etc., 1989-1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Several copies of "Local 1326 Health and Safety News".Correspondence, articles and memos on health & safety concerns, action to be taken and training opportunities. Photo negatives of a few pictures taken for "Bear Facts" articles. Copies of articles from "Bear Facts".
- Health & Safety -- Local cases -- Video Ithaca, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Correspondence about concerns of using Ecco 1500, film cleaner. Copy of MSDS for Ecco 1500.
- Health & Safety -- Local cases -- Watkins Glen killings, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Newspaper clippings about the shooting of 4 Social Service Workers in Watkins Glen.